(Raj:)Hey. Thanks
for coming by.
(Leonard:)Yeah. I'm excited to help.
(Raj:)I would have included
the others, but...
(Raj:)you know exactly
what would've happened.
(Raj:)They would've taken over the
project and bossed us around.
(Leonard:)I get it.
(Leonard:)Uh, just this morning, Sheldon
wouldn't let me put almond milk
(Leonard:)on my Grape-Nuts because he said
(Leonard:)it was
a theoretical nut conflict.
(Raj:)You should have told him
to mind his own business.
(Leonard:)Yeah. That's better
than what I did say, which was,
"Fine, I'll eat them
with club soda."
(Raj:)What makes them think they're
always in charge of everything?
(Leonard:)Mmm, they're alpha males.
(chuckles)
What does that make us?
(Leonard:)We could be betas.
They're second in charge.
(Raj:)Okay, that sounds good.
(Leonard:)Or we could be omegas.
(Leonard:)They get pushed around
by the alphas and the betas.
(Raj:)Okay, that sounds like us.
(Leonard:)Whatever. There's
no alphas here,
(Leonard:)and this is
your project.
(Leonard:)You're in charge.
How do you want to start?
(Raj:)I don't know.